hello yeah I just got uh wow yeah I probably shouldn't be like you know
saying like you know that I'm getting these deliveries but I do want you know
you guys to know that he's wasting these people's time they look very
disappointed it doesn't bother me it bothers them because he's wasting their
The fucking jerk this guy is, um, that's sending all these deliveries to my house and, uh, there's the third one today.
Um, they just look very disappointed when they hear me need to leave.
Hey, what's up, Chona? How are you? Hey, Samantha. Hey, hello. Hello, everybody.
Yeah, it's just a little bit crazy, but, uh, I thought I'd go on one more time. One more time tonight. Hey, hello.
Yeah, you wanna come up, Chona? Um, you can, um, let me see, I'll put my link up.
Um, hi guys.
Oh shit.
Ha, oh, I'll play the ghost song.
Okay.
I got the ghost song ready.
Let me see.
Ghost song.
Let's do the ghost song.
Um, ghosty.
You like the first one though, right?
Okay.
I need to just one second.
Okay, add.
Okay.
Here it comes.
Yeah, this is a ghost song
We're in ghost sober guys, you know, it's the second day of ghost sober, you know
so
Everyone say hi to everybody
Yeah, I swore it was true you laughed it off said psyche. I'm just me not that dude
You're ready to crash out when the moment feels right
Top-donator energy you light up the night big brother in the chat with that wild grin
Every time you roll in the fun begins. Thank you ghost. I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
You're stiff and you're quick, fire-mind
And your quickfire mind
From the late night chaos to the morning light
You've been here holding it down just right
If there's a hall of fame for the real and true
I'd carve your name in Gold Ghost
That's you
I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
You know you do
You're funny as hell, yeah
It's always a blast
These moments we're making
Are built to last
Thank you, ghost
You're one of a kind
With your big heart it mischief
And you quit
Not Tony, huh? All right, Ghost, I believe you. Maybe.
Nerd!
Ah, played that, uh, longer. There you go. There you go. Oh, there we go. Hey, Ghostie.
Hi. Serious question. Does anyone remember Ghost making any... Yes, Ghost is hilarious.
Well, that's what guys not tomorrow, but a Saturday. We're gonna have a party. Yes, everyone's invited
I'm gonna need a costume for ghost sober. I think I need to
Should I you know, I should put my camera on, you know, the big Tony and I should put a camera
I should actually do it. That'd be awesome. I love that
Do it
Well, that's about it. That's about it. The only cause is my habit. I actually have this. This is my ghost
ghost mask. Yeah, oh
Shit
It's scary good job on time
So I give a watch the movie the purge
I've watched a couple of them am I I kind of like them, but it's like it's kind of like
But
Has a weird message behind it. Hey, where's mine? I have a cool lighter. You're gonna love this later. Look at this letter says
See it you motherfucker
I've got a big day today. Hey, what's up everybody? Yeah, we got Chona in here tonight. What's up? I'm a gay skeleton
Oh my gosh, Godie Tommy said I did okay if I have to check my I'm streamer for time
Go ahead. Could you check in with DJ Electra? Is she coming Saturday or not? I hope she can you know, I think she probably will
See I'm looking at my block list for Tommy James. He's think yeah, he's not blocked in my block list or nor in my chat
Only I see Casey. Oh Tommy Tommy Tami or Tammy Tami. No, he's not blocked and I took he's not on the other block
Yeah, well, maybe the mother locked him for a reason though. You gotta be careful, brother. What Saturday we're having a ghost tober
party
We're gonna fucking watch
We're gonna debate
open panel and we might watch later. We might watch Hocus Pocus.
Okay, Hocus Pocus.
My favorite Hocus Pocus is like if you ever...
We can actually like, you know, on StreamYard, I can put it on and then we can like, you know, turn off this live stream
and then we can still be back like on StreamYard.
You know, that sounds really good, but I must admit, I like to have an open panel.
I do like to talk to people and I do like to debate them.
You both.
Unless they're being cool, they're being cool. I mean, that's fine.
Yeah, did you know Shona, you know Shona or no? She said it's Sagittarius. She's my friend in the Philippines and she's like
There's really really she's she was singing before you know she does the Madonna songs and she's just like so awesome and
Yeah, who's I think oh you're second again. Yeah, I know she's a Sagittarius. I'm a Capricorn
I have a lot of Sagittarius friends
But you know me dude as long as they're as long as people don't come in bad faith
I'll talk to anyone but if they come in bad faith. They want to debate, you know, I'll fucking debate
I think that we've got all good people that are like, you know, are what are you?
Did you see any of boy I was just on Tommy James tonight, you know
Tommy James I saw him in Kate's when I went there earlier
Then he had a show and guess who was on the panel with me
Yeah, I don't know. Well, sick. Okay. Sick was there, right? You know, sick. Oh my god signal
Oh my god, so that came on he was like said the n-word, but then he like said he was having
Dude, let me say something psych. You know what the worst you know the best thing about him is like
He says n-word like that's the best. He he is fucked up dude
Yeah, there's who is the woman there her name is like Trollicious or something there or not that's not Trollicious
It was like this woman and she was like
I had to get Trollard here on the stick up there. What's her name?
Like guys who was that woman's name and she was like I felt really kind of bad because then I like I think she like she left because I like I think I won
The debate with her because she just like rage quit and because she was calling me F-A-G-G-O-T that what's that?
What's that?
What is what she's like, what is what the uh, the cigar though
I think we're gonna have fun tomorrow, but I think you should reach out
Do you have DJ electors like not number but like email or anything you can reach out to her?
Yes, I can't
I have her on them discord. Yes, I'm on discord. Okay. Okay. Do you have pages this work too?
Yes, I wrote page tonight on this. I think can you reach out to them Saturday? We're gonna have fun
I mean I shouldn't say that because you know people are probably gonna try to debate me, but no no bullshit
We're gonna have fun. Yes. We will have a lot of fun. I'm already know. Hey, there's Rudy over there eating and
Lola's right here here. You like Lola
You know what I'm gonna eat to celebrate it Saturday morning
What fish taco? Oh, oh fish taco day. I may have to go pick up some from the restaurant if I can't maybe maybe
How long when's the last time you ate a fish taco a cup a few weeks
Well, not the pier it's been a few months, but then I had one at the restaurant with with
I'm talking about the pier the pier. Yeah, I've had one a couple months ago
Yeah, we're a 24-hour stream a guy. I I don't know
Saturday I'm down I'll stay with you
24 hours is a long time for me
The only thing I would ever ask the side could we ever like Saturday if we did that just like give me permission
Like to add people because like people are always trying to come up when you're sleeping. We can't add them
I can't kick it in my head.
And it's like, I think people might try to like,
come on and break TOS or something, and it's like,
I'm just like, I just need to be there, like,
supervisor.
That's an Instagram.
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go backstage,
I'll be backstage and I'll let you on the, on the front
and run things if you want, like, you know, totally.
Because Ghost is, you know, he is sponsoring this year's.
No, no, no, no, I'm not a good guy.
I don't want to bless you.
I'm not a good guy.
No, he's not a good guy, but he's sponsoring this year's like I'm actually Tony. Oh my god. Oh
My gosh, and I don't mean Tony Stark. I'm telling I would get a lot of memberships about 24 hours. I'm a stream
Oh, I'll try but I might be like, you know asleep part of the time, but um, you should give me like
Thank you ghost you Tony. I know it. I mean, I'll do okay. I promise you there'll be an I think I don't
Think they'll be a new a new ghost song. Maybe I'll try to do a new a new ghost song and
You know what I showed I showed the first one to my mom
And I did I did show her the second song where she's like, thank you ghost
And like you want to crack the panels and she's like that's how you are. I was like, I know you raised me
Yes, you want to crash the panels?
It smells good.
It smells like strawberries.
No, I don't want to.
Oh, strawberry-ta!
I'm going to read it tonight.
I should put it in the fridge.
Can I say the G word?
Yeah.
That's fucking gay.
Oh!
Okay.
I think they said the B word, I thought you were going to be a bit, but you know what?
Oh, sorry, I'm sorry, no, I'm sorry, it's a G word, I'm my bad.
I was always calling her, her name was Cringesaurus, and this woman was like, you're at F-A-G-G-O-T,
she did it about a hundred times, and I was just like, and then I started calling her name,
but then I started calling her.
I wish I could turn on my camera side, because you know what, I just said that was the G word, guess what?
It's okay
You have a good heart to Jonah like oh my gosh guys Jonah you have to check out Jonah's channel
It's Jonah adventure
Vlogs and she has a lot of people from all over the world there and it's like if you guys have channels and stuff, you know
Me and I do like I'm a dumb I read this shit like I don't read the comments
There's a way to the watch the chat to you, but
Yeah, you can log in through the stream yard, if you go to the chat it will say the private chat
But then it's like you click the top and it will say like the public chat. I think and then you can see the chat
Can do you feel bad if I address your like even if they have a wrench when I address them? Is that cool?
Of course you can address anybody
Yeah, but you better but be polite to Chona because you know, she's a sweet sweet lady and it's like I know there's like a lot of trolls here
Can I address somebody else
Anybody but you can address anybody as long. Yeah, go ahead
When do we even talk to Jay dog? Oh Chona?
I need to mug you Chona by the way because you're not a mod for some reason
I don't know because I want you to post your link and stuff and
Give you the heart brother. You're good
There you go. Hey, what do you know? Why haven't the time?
Time is here. He's right. He's a ghost is a suck suck boy. Oh shit. There's
Let me read that
They said what he's a ghost is a suck boy right when you were talking about
Oh, no, I mean you well fuck boy you can join that's cool join I'm at the time say that
Let's try and join. Go ahead and join.
Yeah, I'm relatable.
But guys, I feel bad when I like, because she was like,
I was like, kind of like trying to be funny.
I think she was too, but then I think I got me.
No, it's on. Don't run from it. You better join.
Let's run one.
Because here goes Gotti, our first, this is your life.
Oh, Gotti!
Yeah, can I explain something to you guys?
God, how was the people's podcast by the way may I ask?
You were listening how'd it go?
How did you do sir, that's what I'm asking I don't know I didn't listen to it yet
Yeah, you didn't listen. I don't listen to myself ghost. I just
Know I was talking the whole time
I'm tired of you. I'm gonna see you like honestly, you're not you're not like our Saturday. I came here to explain something real quick about why
Is one of the best streamers on YouTube if I could get a word in I?
Just came from another panel
Yeah, nothing. Nothing. Nobody knows anything about just some some random
I went up there I went up there real quick, right? Now this panel is monetized. They're getting fucking $10 here $20 there $30 here
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whatever
I couldn't even tell you what the fuck they were talking about. It was some bullshit fucking. Who knows what to talk about?
Was it tpp or what was it? No, no, no, no, no, it wasn't tpp
No, no, that was before I went to tpp before that this was after tpp. Okay, so after that I went up there real quick
I'm like, what are you guys doing? What is this? What kind of show is this?
instead of tell me what kind of show it is they're like
Who you who's Goddy who's Goddy you Goddy from the I'm like don't worry about who I am just just
So I can know what kind of show this is he's like oh kick him boom kicked off
Less than 30 seconds. I'm kicked off the fucking panel like you know why
He's getting money every two fucking seconds, right? He doesn't need some random guy up here. Give it him. Shit
Can I get a fucking word in asshole?
Can I crash out Psyche?
Yes or no? Can I crash out?
You crashed out the gate.
Can I crash out?
If I tell the story and then
I'll make you a ghost.
I'll get a pin and I'll pop it.
I'll give you 30 seconds.
I'm almost done yeah, so this guy. Yeah, he's full. They follow themselves over there on the fucking panel
They kick me off like I'm nothing that's why you down to earth you give everybody a chance
Even if they call you a shithead or whatever they call you you still bring them back you forgive them
You give me a chance and you give me this place to talk. Yeah, I'm what's wrong with that?
I don't know why people got a problem with you. It's fine. I'm trying to like create something for everybody not just
I thought I could answer after that
Go ahead, go ahead, Ghost. What do you have to say?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I think I wouldn't trust this motherfucker. He has no idea what the fuck he's talking about. I don't know.
You know, and he's laughing because he knows I'm talking the truth. He has no idea what the fuck he's talking about. I don't know.
You could trust me like
You not remember that it was only like you know like 20 minutes ago. I was there asshole. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, I went one-on-one. You remember that and you were kissing you were fucking rubbing their ass, weren't you?
Oh, was I rubbing their ass was I was I?
Repeat what I said big boy repeat what I said
Oh
You know still up you can all go
You're the best you're the best you're the best, you know that
If you don't mind, I mean no, no, I don't mind go ahead pal
Yeah, I I was there to debate, but you were there and you were just like well, I guess that's what you do though
So I don't really have an argument. That's kind of what you do like you just like troll them. So I don't I don't
Yeah, I guess I don't have an argument. I guess I I guess I can see
You call me a troll
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, what what are you?
Perfect magnificent awesome cool good-looking
Those are all adjectives. What are you?
Would you say how am I or what are said? What are you what what are you?
Are the best at what I do. What do you do?
Chew bubblegum and kick-ass
What is that? Oh, it's that movie
They live you fucking try you went over there you trying to get along fuck. What is he trying to say? He was up there, too
Well, I was trying to be dumb dumb. You were trying to hang out
I wasn't trying to debate. What were you trying to debate though? What were we trying to say?
Think TPB is a bunch of bitches. They're a bunch of not by the way. I'm speaking about myself not psyche, but my claim is
Bunch of bitches. They're a bunch of retards. They're a bunch of dumb-dumbs, and they don't the fuck they're talking about
Why cuz they kicked you out?
They didn't kick me I left you dumb fuck
Like I not call you and be like hey starter panel
Like literally you know
When psyche kicks me off his panel, I say the same shit. I said, yeah, he didn't fucking kick me off. I left
You didn't you didn't follow me up
You got bounced out like a ball
Mean what's the argument? Oh, what are we doing here? Are we going back and forth on bullshit?
No, no, no, I don't really like you. I think you're kind of
Listen, you don't have to fucking like me, but you're gonna
You're gonna fucking respect me
I think you're saying I think you're fucking funny. I think I'm not here to be liked when bag
It's okay. Why are you here at all if you're not here? So why are you here? I'm here to for you to worship me
Okay, well you're done. No, I'm done with you
This guy look at this guy that like it is writing me on
I'm done with you guys. Is he a millionaire? I don't know but he's
Hot
He's writing me on staff
Don't don't do that. He's cute, huh?
Hey, Dougie Doug, how are you good to see you? Dougie Doug's in the house guys
Oh, wow now that now the real excitement begins
Yeah, debate it let's debate if I'm a piece of shit or no, let's go
All right, I'm down to have that debate if you want to have it begin my claim
I think you're a piece of shit. I think that you you go all all these panels, but also
It's not like you're there to have fun. You're there to talk shit. You don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Is that a problem for you?
Very Mason's here, good.
Look at me too.
LD just got out of the shower, hey guys.
Hey Mason, why the long face?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Hey
Any girl Jen Jen or is it a different for Jennifer or something like that? That was fucking good boy
Shout out to God he that
I know what you're doing. Hey, hey, I got you. Remember
What's the matter man the thumb remember the thumb
Stop stop doing it
What do you got?
Where's Mason?
Oh my God, my stomach hurts.
Mason, are you okay?
Mason, come back. I'm sorry, man.
Mason, they're just kidding.
We're having fun with laughing.
Look what you did, God.
What did I do?
Mason, are you crying?
Don't cry, please.
Is he?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
It's because Gaudi is here. That's why I would turn quiet. Let me leave. Let me leave. Let me leave. Let me leave
I'll come back. Okay, God
Psyche Mason you can come back. Oh, I'll leave you Psyche Psyche, you know, I won't get along with Gaudi
That's why I had to turn quiet. So that's why it's a don't turn quiet. Gaudi is a good guy. He just is like
He's kind of like
he's a gruff exterior he's not his bark is worse than his bite i think right no masaki he was being
mean to me that's why he's saying he's a mean person but i still like him
No, it's like I didn't know if they want to but he was actually like I did something wrong to him
I know amazing. You have to get
You're too innocent. I don't I had this I had this I've had these huge
Potomous women screaming that you know at they GGOT at me all week and it's like I can just laugh about it
So you can handle this one Scott Mason. Okay, I promise you I
Can handle it
Yeah, wait, right
Listen, I'm not trying to debate you. I'm not trying to argue with you. I'm not trying to
You're good
Yeah, Mason's edge ghost is gonna be nice. You'd like ghosts Mason
Yeah, he's okay. I think you're good. Well, you're welcome. If you said no, I would have debate
Yeah, so, you know always smile is in the chat and she says she likes Mason, right?
Look look someone like like Mason look she says I like Mason. He's awesome
Wait, I want to tell you something though. Wait, hold on. Thank you. Tell me. It's like sake. Let me tell you something man listening
So like I had no problem. That's like I never had a problem with you
But then I just there's other people that want to you know come at me, and I don't know about the yeah
You know what you just have to like
They come at they come at you because your psyche's friend you're like you're the person you fit in them
That's just how it is me. I do the shit for a living. I mean every day your psyche's boy
Your psyche's right. I do the shit where I live in Mason
You know what a troll is, you know what a troll is, Mason?
What is a troll, man, like, what do you talk about when you say a troll?
It's like everybody in my entire chat is a troll, pretty much.
Even I am a little bit, like, just a little bit.
Yeah, just a little bit.
I'm more of a troll on Instagram.
We should have seen it on Instagram.
I had these two guys dancing.
Then they were like half in their underwear dancing.
And then I turned the thing around and got them to put all their clothes on and get really mad and upset.
It was so funny. And the whole chat turned into trolls too because everyone took my lead because they were making all these gay jokes and stuff. It was so funny.
No, Psyche. No, Psyche, I used to be cool with Gotti, but I don't know about now though because of what he said to me last Thursday.
He was saying all this weird stuff, remember?
Yes, he is. Um, ghost. Oh, my God.
I just heard him say stuff that I couldn't believe that time that God, he was talking to me. I know. I've always shocked. I still am shocked at what he says, but it's like, I'm kind of getting used to it. You have to, like, kind of know more and then it's like,
Yeah, you just happen to like, you know
Mason if you're a good
Listen Mason, I think that if you're a good debater
I think you can take it on their cheek, but you can also give it back
I think that like like psyche's doing he not doing good, but he did better today
The when he put that clip like the you brought up a claim burden proof like when did I do that like show me the proof
I think that's really good. I think that's what we should do Mason like
So I could try to tell me I have to learn from like this kind of stuff. Yeah, it's gonna make you stronger
I promise you I mean why not learn? I mean that's a good question. Why not learn?
We had a reviler red in this morning and reviler red was wow. He was just I mean that guy is a dick
I mean, but he's still
Mason can I Mason are you trolling are you at are are you trolling?
So I guess I'm just being no, it's like I'm just being normal man. I'm just trying to be here just to you know hang out
He has normal intelligence, he's just like socially awkward a little bit
Mason NYPD
No, it's like, it's like, I can't, I can't help the way I talk, man.
I have like problems.
I'm sorry.
Oh, well, you don't understand anything, and you do understand, and you're very smart
to saying like that you're not used to this kind of trolls and stuff like that, but it's
good to like learn a little bit, right?
Yeah, that's what I was saying earlier so I got saying it's something I can actually learn from like what goes on with other
Like people that try to tell me stuff. I don't get can't believe
Mason is actually smarter than everybody
He's also like a great drummer, like I saw his
Anybody in a in a band
He's like a genius and instruments actually so
You're laughing
Just but in drumming and like memory and stuff
But it then it's like but you're really good at that and then it's like and some other things you need to like learn more about right?
Yeah, yeah
That's yeah
Saki, but what happened though? Why did that guy leave though? He left. He's he's his phone's always dropping out
He may have gone gone and do something in the chat. Hey, you know, you know, Chona Chona is
That she's a Sagittarius in the chat. She's from the Philippines. She's saying hi to you. I think she's giving you the heart pace
She likes you
So I can never heard of that person. Oh, it's new to me. Yeah, she's no you have to say oh here comes ghosts back
Just say hi say hi Chona
Huh say hi to Chona
Hi to Chona. Yeah. Say hi, Chona. Hi, Chona. There you go.
She's a Sagittarius person in chat. She's in the Philippines. You know where that is?
It's like in Indonesia still, like where yummy is, similar to where yummy is.
Yeah, near Yumi. It's a different country, but it's nearby.
Yeah, she's she's a similar to work. Like her name is like a cat zilla like ready. Yeah, okay. That's layer
Mason why'd you get quite like you psyche? I don't have a problem though, but there's God
Address me don't address them address me
Gaudi, I'm just here just to be with my friends like you. That's why I'm here. That's fine
But you made an accusation against me. I want to answer this right now. I
Don't understand like how to make it
You don't understand you just made an accusation against me about five minutes ago. You want me to run it back?
You said I made an accusation. What do you mean? Yeah, you came up here. You said you didn't like what I said last time
I was on the panel with you
I don't even know what I said to you and you've just made up a whole story right there
You told me but you told me if I didn't want to make fun of you then you said you weren't gonna make fun of me though
You're trying to castigate me as some kind of bad guy
Thank you. What do I do here, man?
It's okay Mason, you know you just say say fuck you gotty. No, no, I want him to explain himself
Okay, Mason why tell God he what he said that upset you
Sike, yeah, I don't know how to explain myself man. I already told him like what's going on
It's the what do you say? What do you say exactly that you didn't like?
He said he said he's gonna not he said he's gonna make fun of me if I didn't want him to make fun of me
The stuff like that. Well, does that you just like, you know save so what that doesn't even make sense. Yeah
Mason, come on, stick in there, Mason.
Come on, stick up for yourself.
Hurry up, Mason, before this guy starts talking,
once the power starts going, nobody can shut him up.
Hurry up.
Gotti, Gotti, I didn't, no, Gotti,
I'm not trying to be rude to you or anything, man.
It's just, I get my feelings like, you know, like,
hurt easily, man.
Oh, you're very sensitive.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, I'm a sensitive person, Gotti.
I don't mean to be, though.
You're not the only one.
I'm just, that's the way I am.
They're not the only one.
There's a lot of fucking sensitive people
running around this place.
Yeah, but God he don't take it
Mason listen Mason you want me to take care of body for you. I
Don't know. I don't know God. He got it. You're okay right now
Gosh guys
People that's how you squash beat
As soon as I joined, God, you behave.
Good boy.
You don't have to go and make a panel.
Hate for 10 hours of hate.
You don't have to do all that stuff.
You can just come up.
No, God, I just got confused that day.
End it.
No, it's like, I mean, God, I just got confused that day.
That's why I was acting like that.
So I thought something was wrong.
I'm glad I can un-confuse you.
OK.
Congratulations.
Yeah, but I mean, I'll give you another chance, man. Oh, thank you lord. Thank you. Thank you me
Thank you me for another nice of him
Shut the fuck up, Cody go back to your corner. Okay, don't address me. Okay, you lowlifes come back
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
Don't be like Sam and it'd be a fucking money grubba
Hey in Mason so
Ducky Doug says tell the chump Goddy to go fuck himself. Can you say that me only only if he pays?
No, no, Goddy. No, Goddy. I don't want to say anything to offend you though. That's why I don't want to say
What are you kidding me
Got it. Have I ever offended you one time? Yeah, there's one day. I did only one
I don't know what I said. I forgave you. I forgave you here comes. Here's come ghostie. Whoa
Thank you ghost. I won't forget you
Yeah, cool. I got a problem though. I do have a problem Godie. It's like you. Oh, you got a problem, too
Let me explain my problem before you talk if you don't mind. Well, I'm not talking. I have a problem. You start talking
Go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. Go. Let's go
You guys want to talk shit about Mason, but uh
There's no I got his back. What's running? I
Know I have Mason's back
He's a bully
Hey, I'm going to defend your two.
Let's, we can all go against Gotti.
Looky, looky, looky.
If you guys want a gang bang, Mason.
Organs won.
We're going to have a gang bang.
Got to be quiet, and throw a ring, and they go,
oh, oh, oh, Mason, we won.
He ran away, he raged quick.
Yes, Mason, you won.
You beat Gotti.
I'm not going to say a slur.
Can I call Gotti a slur, if you guys don't mind?
Psyche, Psyche, we actually won this.
Psyche's not winning right now.
You dumb fuck.
You scared him away
Yes, you do
I
Once you like get to know him. It's like he's not really trying to like
You shouldn't have done making like that that dude's he's retired. He's can I say he retired it man? I mean, he's not retarded
But you guys
Beat him up kick him off the panel who you guys were to you guys ganked up on
Yeah, psyche. So what's what's going on now? Like everybody's like uh, like on my side or no. Yeah, everyone's on your side
Having fun
Yeah. You don't even speak English. We're gonna make you a master at talking about here.
You're gonna be a master at troll, Mason?
I'm psyching. I'm psyching. I was just trying to make things better, though, again.
I was trying to make it back to normal again.
Well, it's kind of too late for that because teams are way out of control always.
But you know what? I like it. I like it a little bit chaotic.
You know what chaos is, Mason?
So like you don't mind it to be a little crazy like in your chat or on your panel
Normal and everyone's just getting along perfectly a little bit of a little bit of fun
By the way Mason, you're invited Saturday. We're gonna have a party. You're invited Mason
And you want to come with me when I come to the party on Saturday Mason everyone's
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, what does that mean?
You just you just talk back to him and then like and then remember, you know, you just talk back and then you're just laugh
Nobody cares dude come you're very welcome by the way. I'm sure cycle degree with me. You're very welcome. Of course
Everyone's welcome. I mean, it's like, you know, as long as, you know, everyone is like
Everybody I think we're gonna put I think we're gonna throw some money down. I'm not we're not gonna block anyone, but I think
You know
I might give ghosts a little bit of a little bit of kicking power on a psyche
I could come over and play video games with you, right? We can all play video games together
Mason god damn Mason, I don't know if you're trolling or not. Are you trolling?
So like yeah, I'm not trolling. I'm being serious
But he's learning learning the video game. This is a new kind of
If you go to if you go to a place and play video games, you give you
Loans you just like I'll complain with it
So
Do you want to play Mason? What do you want to play?
Okay, we can do it
Hey
Oh here comes. Oh look who these back. Oh, here is
Hello
LD do you like Mason or no?
No, we're Mason go. Oh
Wow
Is that an anime character? I
Saw woman that's his good psyche. That's his girlfriend man. It looks like it's girlfriend. Oh, wow
It looks like he's about ready to get a little handy
So I get it looks like a woman club it towards him. Yeah, it does
That's a woman right LD
Yes, she definitely is so I can watch so I can watch you not
Oh, yeah, oh, look at that tattoo. That's cool. What is that Jack Nicholson? Who is that? Oh
My gosh
Wow, so like you so like you why is he not answering you though? He's he I think he's speechless
Everyone close your eyes and recover your eyes. I don't know what's gonna happen to this pajama pants. Hey look it goes crashed out
Okay, it goes crashed out. Whoa
Yeah, she's pretty LD. She's gorgeous. What's her name?
So like he said his girlfriend though the woman is right
She looks like Sailor Moon or like, you know one of the Sailor Moon characters the hair. It's cool
Okay, so you'd like to have a little bit of fun in your street, right?
If it goes a little crazy, or something.
I want to have a lot of fun.
Let's all get in LD's room right now.
I'm just kidding.
Okay, hey, I want to join.
Come on, I'm just kidding.
Hold on, who's in the backstage?
I'm sorry, this is going insane.
Okay, here comes God.
And look, Chris will go soon.
Thank you, what are you going to do to her?
I don't know.
But Psyche, why is her hair pink like that?
I think it's an actual color.
But Psyche, do you think they're going to use condoms?
Hey, Psyche.
But Psyche, why is LD on the bed and she's not?
Watch and find out.
Let's figure it out.
But Psyche, why does she keep moving away from him?
Look what's going on, Psyche.
But Psyche, why is he filming this?
Look at his feet.
You like feet mason remember you show me your feet once mason. No, no psyche. I'm not trying to get into that
You're not okay. It's okay. No, it's like I mean I mean like psyche. I mean in a good way though
I'm not trying to get a virtual reality. I like this. I feel I feel like I am a MLD right now. It's POV
IRL POV
Yeah, oh
Like that mason look at that
Thank you. That's a good woman. Right? It is a good woman. Yeah.
What do you think, Chat? I think we all approve.
Thank you. Why is he showing her off though? He's like trying to show her off.
Because look at how hot she is. It's called I can. Oh, look at she's her weekend bag.
I see leopard print. Wow, this is good.
Mason, you brought up a good point.
I wouldn't show her off either.
That's not what you guys wanted to do.
No, no psyche.
The reason why I said that is because that belongs only him,
though, that woman.
Oh, last time we saw a coat like that, he pissed on it.
Is that a box of magnums?
Hey, be careful.
He pissed on a coat like that about six months ago.
Look at the black light.
I feel like I'm okay. We're walking to the room. Okay
Nice and you like you watch you get her clothes all ready and stuff
She about to take a shower or what she doing?
I'm not sure well, she she takes off too many if she takes off her clothes. I might have to turn you know
Turn my head. Hey
Yeah
This is called IRL, guys. This is like the real, this is like better than a video game.
Is this better than, you know, your Mortal Kombat, Mason?
Well, that's what he's wearing.
So I can't know.
So I can't know about that. I mean, I like video games a lot though.
It's more like an adult game, I think.
Yeah, this is a different kind of game. Psyche is not a video game.
Here we go.
You know what I'm saying? Sonneke is different than a video game. This is like real people. Yeah, you gotta love a bed
We're just a bed in it
Looks like she's coming she's moving in oh
That's the dress
Check all those banks can I can I wear that Mason?
How do I look in that?
Look at those heels, look at how big the heels are.
Stop doing that.
What is that?
Sike, what do you want to wear, man?
We don't wear those.
There's heels, the walking stick, and the dress.
That's a pimp cane.
Yeah, oh yeah.
Booby canker.
You have a pimp cane?
Eldie gets out of hand.
She just gives him a little whack.
Yeah, I'm gonna slap you guys cuz you guys don't oh my god. He's showing her ass for us
Play it back
Is that a way she's wearing
She's she's white or Japanese I can't suck so I guess she has tattoos all over
They might be retarded, I mean I'm not trying to be
Was that a tattoo of Hannibal Lecter on Iran?
They dumb dumb arbor, or ghost one.
Not me.
That was my Hannibal Lecter.
The happy couple.
Yeah, psyche psyche LD is not really saying much to you though. He's just
The fridge, please can I see the
In his mind right now
They live
Yeah, I guess it is good that sometimes I guess it is good sometimes to not say anything, right just to do stuff
Howdy, are you banning people in the chat? No, I don't ban people
God he's timing people out. Well, fuck you asshole. How about that?
Fucking business you dumb fuck
You told me that, man.
Enjoy the show.
Enjoy the fucking show.
Someone in the chat, Mason.
People are stupid, man.
Mason is the new star of the panel, I think.
What is that?
A full-size bed?
She's going on camera.
She's about to take off her bra, I think.
She's pissed.
Oh, she's like, get out of here.
Yeah, she kicked him out.
Hey, Gardy, yeah, I do I do I'm not gonna lie to you if you guys would excuse me. I do have to pee
My god, how much money you got I got
God I see what's going on man with twinkle silver, right? That's who told you that yeah
Let's go Jason are you twinkle silver in the chat?
That's not me. I'm mason a drummer man. Is that the real
That's the fake black RG black RG the real black RG
Say something right now and it says build GEE
Yeah, that's a difference spelling. I need to mod the real black. I don't think you I don't think you'd be such a pussy to say such a pussy thing like that
Well, we should change your name to put in that kill
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Who are you? Are you drunk?
Are you are you drunk? Are you
I don't know man. I don't know okay. I don't know. Close your eyes Mason. Close your eyes.
Are you old enough to watch this movie, Mason?
Mason, you just watched before.
Wait, what psyche am I old enough to watch?
Watch this movie.
Unbelievable.
That was good.
Mason, close your eyes.
I saw this on a donkeywalk since soon.
That's fucking good.
It's good.
That was good. That was a good
one. I give you that. That was
a good one. I will give you that.
You won. You won the debate. That
was fun. How much drugs do you
think they got? Is there drugs
in there? I'm hoping. I want some.
Is that an Arizona iced tea?
Uh oh. She's got one of those
There's Jonah's still here. What's up Jonah? What a try Jonah?
Can I talk please let me speak Jonah come up and sing
Are you coming to ghost party tomorrow?
That's a real bird, that's a real bird, was it any animal harm you're making of that?
That's where it was made for.
No, it's been a crash out.
That's possible.
I'm forming.
I'm not coming. I'm not coming.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I see that psyche. Yeah, I could see them
Yeah
Leprechaun hat we can't hear you LD. You know that, right? I'm gonna turn my camera on I'm gonna say work
Yeah, yeah
We're doing it now goes tell me when you know
Oh
I'm gonna say that word. I'm
gonna say that word. I'm gonna
say that word. I'm gonna say
that word. I'm gonna say that
word. I'm gonna say that word.
I'm gonna say that word. I'm
gonna say that word. I'm gonna
say that word. I'm gonna say
that word. I'm gonna say that
word. I'm gonna say that word.
I'm gonna say that word. I'm
gonna say that word. I'm gonna
say that word. I'm gonna say
Can I say the F word? Yes or no?
I'm gonna say a slur
Go ahead ghosts you paid
That's why this is the best dream
You know, what's wrong with that there's nothing wrong with saying that
I think I just heard
Hey, God, do you drink fireball man? Do you drink? I don't drink Mason. No, okay. I'm having strawberry rica
strawberry what?
Yeah, he guzzles he's down guzzle him. He says cheers first
What the fuck are you doing
He just said cheers
He's wearing a woman's you're wearing my fucking dog's coat. That's his mother's for a coat
I think it used to be I was used to be like I'm one of those
Alaskan sheepdogs or the last you look like a TV version of like 101
Dalmatians, but like worse than 99, you know, I'm saying like that's why cheers LD cheers
No
Now he's now you can fuck until he's like drunk
Is he not attracted to women?
So he has to get really drunk to bang these girls
I broke to us. Oh my god
Did you hear me? No, I didn't
hear you. I said, do you drink
any kind of alcohol, Gotti? No, I
said, no, I don't. Well, what do
you drink then? This regular
sodas? Or what do you drink? I
drink water.
We're having fun tonight. This
is called ghost. Hey, ghost.
Come on.
Hey, ghost.
I'll stop. I'll stop my bad.
I'm so sorry. Fuck it, I'll send it to you, you know what, I'll send it to people chatting, my god, I feel bad.
Gaudi, Gaudi, I understand waters, Gaudi, I understand waters good for you and stuff like that, but not all the time though, except that gets old.
It does get old, but you can put a little bit of tequila in it, it tastes great.
Oh, that's a bad angle.
Oh, come on, it's like you say Mason when you say yeah, you know the word yet. You say no yet
Yeah, thank you. What is that? Like yeah, damn like that
Saki is that a good angle? Yeah, it's great angle
What do you think?
The god he doesn't seem to think it's a good angle. He that was a flattering. I'm a I must I'm a cinnamon dog
Right, this girl's sick of everything you can see how she's pointing
Well, yeah
Get that get that get that bug on the wall then the heat up
She says turn around and bend over near the wall. Honey. Well, holy shit. How old is that thing? That's a 1970s. Jesus. Yeah, that's an oldie
Whoo, how is everybody anything? I need to drink. I need to chug this strawberry Rita and get in the party mood
Psyche so water is the best thing, huh? What are you drinking mason?
The I don't not drink anything right now, but I'm just saying water's probably the best thing to drink
It is a good thing. Hey, but it's okay
That's a curse jar. He's tipping in now guys
Curse, you know all his example. That's a super chat five bucks
Then I'll forgive you
It's the answer. That's from the 70. Oh, thank God Apollo left. Oh, yeah, Paul is gone
So it's just LD God
God, how do you know if he left because you can't see anybody in the you know, like
Isn't here that voice I don't hear him fucking breathing and choking on his own voice
Hey, oh, yeah, a dr. You know chro. I mean, oh, of course, you know all about it, Nick
Oh, we can't say that either. Well, I'd like to spell it out because it's a little bit controversial
People don't even know what it is unless they do know God. Are you a coffee drinker, man? No, no, I don't drink coffee either
There's somebody there's somebody in the chat that said drink coffee though
I don't drink coffee though. That's always smile is a coffee drinker. I like a coffee, too, but
I have like you know some coffee left. I might have a rare tea but a bunch of
Irish cream into it and drink it
Oh, we got a crucible ghost is back. Yeah, I don't need drugs to get by that includes
What's up?
Hey
Let's see, but she's robbing in Georgia stands aside. Yeah
He's gonna wake up naked tied to the bed with his wall missing that
I'm just kidding
Can I wear that Mason how would I look in that black tank top?
Hey, Mason, are you pecking on the chat, Mason?
It says Mason Second Skin, that's you.
Oh, look at that, look at that, look at that.
She's got the long story.
Wait, Saki, wait, what?
Look at the screen, is that you in the chat?
No, I'm not that.
Yeah, that's for sure, I recognize you.
It says Mason Second Skin, and it's a picture of your shirt.
No, Saki, no, Saki, somebody took that picture
and then must have uploaded it on there.
That's not me, though.
It's not, that's your shirt, I recognize it.
So somebody must have did that though. So I can somebody took that picture. Hey Mason, you're famous
You already have it. You already have a clone in the chat. It's cool. Look at there's a little troll
Why are you Tony?
Why are you gonna be Mason? What's that guy?
Gut going you know, is your name Tony?
No
Hey chubby are you correct?
She pregnant already LD. I think she's pregnant already leave her alone. Goddy. She can't hear me
She can't hear me the sounds looking at you at the mean look
Happily married yes or no, is she happily?
I'll get all of them, all of them.
Hold on, who is that?
Is that Jack Nicholson on the tattoo?
It looks like the guy from Signs of the Lamps.
Oh, it's Anthony Hopkins.
That's cool.
Is it?
Yeah.
Oh, that was a good move.
Why does he got a tit?
Psyche.
He's got a Psyche.
Yeah.
It was Ghost.
Thank you. Why does he have a kid? He's in the chat. He's in the chat. He's like he's an actual ghost like you know Casper
He's like his cousin. Yeah, no, but psyche Hanna said
Hanna said something like good
Like
She was asking if somebody has to Tourette's psyche like yeah
Listen dumb fuck you read the comments. You didn't bring up a original thought, but do I have Tourette's? No, I don't say
I have I have. Oh, look at that.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
She's a hood rat. She's a hood
and it says keep your fantasy
like fire. Stick to the chat,
you're don't talk to me like
that. You're no better. Mason,
why do you ask Natty for pictures
of uh oh. Oh god, Pete. The
LD how big your feet LD 13s Wow
She said they smelled earlier. They smell better now
Long long big toes
He doesn't eat that I'm not on camera now because I'm a little bit
That's why him and Shannon didn't get along because you had to
Look at your tattoos when I first met you and you were showing me your tattoos
Look at his legs
We started talking to me off in a crash out
Big lips. Don't we all you know every every uh saint has a past every sinner has a future
That's my that's my motto and every retard has a you know future. I mean, you know, we get that from a fucking Snapple cap
Yeah
How old is she? No, she's uh, she looks like she's about 21. She said she was 17
Listen listen who needs to have sex they haven't seen each other in 10 years who needs to have sex
She's just gonna sit there and fold clothes for like five hours. Let's forget sex. Who needs sex? I do
Well, you're not gonna get it from these two
Well, I can at least we're gonna get it from Gandhi. Keep going. I can't watch you get the red ghost. That's your job
I just want to say I just want to sit in the corner with a bottle of lube. Okay?
Fuck it. I get five dollars. Watch you. I'll throw five bucks Gandhi if you want to go to a crash out
I'm finna crash out. I'm not gonna lie. Do it. Let's all do it. Let's all crash out. I'm finna crash out
I don't know. I don't know.
Who is who is 535 in the? I
don't know. Have you ever
crashed out? What do you mean?
Have you ever crashed out? Yeah,
you may like sleep like you
Calm
Ghosts all the time
He's just retarded
I'm like thank you. Thank you. I'm not retarded. Thank you. I just don't know what that is not calling you retarded
I'm sorry
Dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb. He's calling. He's like with the lollipops. You like this? Yeah, put you on my lap
I'm not gonna miss the mustache
Oh, I'll put you on my lap. Yeah, get a marker and draw a new one on
Yeah, I'll shake your beard. You don't even have a beard, but I'll put you on my lap.
Oh, Natalie's coming up.
I'll put you on my shirt.
Now the real fun begins.
Natalie.
Let's go.
I love, I love, I love, I love LD's like little, little gap in his teeth.
I love that.
That's not what you said to me last night, you're...
I'm super attracted to, like, a gap in the teeth.
You said you want me.
I'll never forget who you met.
When Sike and Press met at LD, oh my god.
Hey, Sike.
Yeah.
How could somebody have my second skin, though?
I don't get how somebody can act like they're me
in the subject.
He's talking about your shirt, Mason.
He's talking about the only shirt you got in your house.
Oh, that's him, sir.
Mason, I can act like you if you don't mind.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
That's not her psyche. That's a porn bomber. Yeah, that's a video. That's how they do it now
They show you a video of something that you think you like and then they boom hit you with that's her
Natalie can you say hi to the camera?
It's fake, right?
That's fake, right?
Hey, got it
You're a second
It's funny the first three times but after that
They actually made a fake person that looks like her. Yeah, that's how they do it
They make a fake person that you wave to make sure you're real and then it hits you off with oh wait
They let you left. Oh my god. It was a big Natalie, but I told you
That word got me stop saying that I invented this shit
That was a fake Natalie, I think no, I think she I think it was just froze cuz God God. Yeah, I think God
Oh my god, I don't get a guy. I think I know what happened
It was somebody that was trying
to be here because like they
know that I'm actually in the
in the panel. I think they
did that. They're wearing her
skin. I guarantee nobody cares
about you. Who's this guy?
That's LD.
Fuck out D. He's a dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb
Oh, these are fucking bit rape glasses. He's wearing the rape glasses tonight. She's gonna have a good time
It's not great, sir. Oh, sorry
That's
And show your girl, show your girl, show your girl again.
Tattoos, hair wig, all those tattoos.
You're a fucking weirdo.
God, he stuck up his metal figure.
Yeah, fucking hair wig, tattoos.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha, I'm always right.
God damn, ghost always wins.
God damn it, I'm always correct.
Fucking weirdo.
You still there?
God, are you still there?
Yeah, I'm trying to be here.
Yeah, I'll meet yourself dumb fuck Audi. I'll meet yourself dumb dumb
No, I wanted to unmute yourself. I would like to have the conversation
I don't know. Oh, I don't know
I don't know. I don't know.
That's gonna crack down. I don't remember last time you had a party up here because nobody came it was just you and Psyche
You're gonna you're gonna try to join but guess what I'm gonna tell you're not you're not joining either you're not
Nobody came to your party, dude. I was there Psyche. Yeah
Now they said that her Wi-Fi was kind of cutting in and out though. That's what she said
Come on up L. D. You're muted, sir. I want to hear I want to hear you
I'm you or fix you want to be on camera the girl doesn't want to talk. Yes. I don't know how to read lips
I just am like looking at your tongue. She's the boss
Hey, you fucking retarded sir, it's you just said it's like one button that's caught on you whenever LD meets a new girl
He just hands his balls over to them right away
No, no look at her
And a Natalie's back. Oh
Left
Let's go
Go so he's one. Oh here he is. He's back
Thank God, let's warm up. Oh, we can't hear you, dude
Listen sir, I'm gonna be myself you push
Well, then you push your button now and now I'm on mute it if you're gonna wear those clothes all night. Let's go chop chop
Hey Natalie, hello, hello, how are you?
Yeah, you're not given by the way there. I'm not using that
You look like every dumb dumb fingers. Yeah
Well, I'm finna crash out
Fingers on that three fingers on a movie on internet
Why have I issued? Hey, how many fingers can I use on you? Hey, oh D?
No, I mean I got 20 bucks
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding, I'm just
I made licks. What do you mean by licks? To get to the center of the titsy bop. I don't know, man
three
Natalie got the answer before you said it
They've scientifically done it just say it will the owl licks it twice and then he bites it and so it's oh, yeah
He's cheating
Why is he up here nobody even likes those
I like them. They're good. Yeah. No, the blow pop. Thank you. I do like the gum
You know, I can like I can like turn a blow pop. I can like chew it until it turns white
psyche
Do you care so I can do you even care?
I know I just want to know how you thought Natalie are you there?
I'll so much Natalie
Guys I think I'll be talking
Yes, shut up all night. Oh
Stop hyping up LD. Oh, no shit. Stop it. Don't say that
You gotta meet yourself dumb fuck good
Now his wife is not good
Was I the one you're talking about that didn't stop talking like during the whole night
Are you having a party? Yeah, we're a memes like he's having party Mason
Well, you're not invited sir. No, what time?
24 hours. 24 hours. 24 hours.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll make sure I'm
not around. Oh, God. Why are
you going to make sure you're
not around? I don't want to be
there. I'll be right back. I'm
going to be with CB.
Oh, you are you are are you like are you gonna mean CB? You're gonna have a monster party. You're not sex with CB
No, I said we're gonna have a monster party
What does that mean? That means all monsters
Sees the guest of honor. Oh
G crucible girls. Are you doxxing that address? Let me see that address again
He looks like
You're not gonna talk yeah, they put the finger to your throat like you're gonna cut our throats
We can't hear you dumb fuck. I'll meet yourself. It's not that hard brother
You see where it says microphone you gotta click it don't look at her
You beat up a transgender man
Click the fucking button we can't hear you dumb
Dumb dumb. He's gonna do it again tonight. No damn it. Here we go
Like the fucking on you please or maybe you have like a round what they got it
I think I think something happened man
What happened?
Like our G is like our G in the chat man. No, he's not there
Oh, I thought he was in the chair. That was you
That wasn't me I trace that I traced that back to your account that was you I
Don't want to say anything, but you brought it up again
Wait, where'd that bring up Mason? I got a degree in cyber security. Listen. I don't need to play these games with people
So God I didn't do anything man. Yeah, you tried to fucking paint me as a bad person
When did what did that happen? I thought we were done with that get it up on the panel
And then you went down there is black fake black RG you try to do it down there
No, that wasn't me. God. Yeah, I don't know what you told me. It was you Mason. It was you
No, it wasn't we traced the account back to your IP address. All right. I
Don't know what you're talking about. Okay. All right. You want to play stupid. That's fine
Now you look bad
Dude, just stop man
No
Got it. Don't make me get mad man. I don't want to get mad
No, listen Mason Mason you're pissing me off right now, and you don't want no Gotti stop it dude
Got it really stop Mason for real. I'm getting sick of this shit right now. No Gotti. God. I don't know
Good thing good thing. I'm not playing with you, dude
Because you're about to fucking lay yourself up flat. I'm about to knock you out
Because you keep talking like an idiot
You're gonna bang your head against the wall
God he don't make me guy. Don't make me kill you man. I'll kill you dude. I'll friggin murder you dude
You're gonna kill your throat Godie. I'm not playing man
Taste the biscuit